(Bernadette:)Well, it's just, after last time,
(Bernadette:)I didn't think you'd
ever want to go back.
(Howard:)Are you kidding? It was the greatest
experience of my life.
Really? 'Cause I kind of
remember a lot of complaining
(Bernadette:)and wishing for it to be over.
(Howard:)I think you have me confused
(Howard:)with what's gonna happen when
you get out of that shower.
(Leonard:)Hey, all set.
What do you think?
(Leonard:)There's plenty of room for everybody,
a view out the window.
(Sheldon:)My spot on the couch
has a great view of a window.
(Sheldon:)Sometimes I can see
space battles through it.
(Sheldon:)It's called a TV.
(Penny:)Give it a chance, Sheldon,
you might actually like it.
(Sheldon:)You're absolutely right.
(Sheldon:)Nope.
(Penny:)Well, you can't say he
didn't give it a fair shot.
(Sheldon:)So, when can we get rid of it?
(Sheldon:)We're not.
(Sheldon:)What about the roommate agreement?
(Sheldon:)It specifically states
that any changes in furnishing
(Sheldon:)have to be approved
by the Furnishing Committee.